6scan.com 2017-05-07

# 6Scan – Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is critically important to us. At 6 Scan we have a few fundamental principles:  
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)  
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:  
If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.  
It is 6 Scan’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, 6 Scan Software Ltd collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 6Scan’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how 6Scan’s visitors use its website. From time to time 6 Scan Software Ltd may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
6 Scan Software Ltd also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users of our site protection services. 6 Scan Software Ltd only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to 6Scan’s websites choose to interact with 6 Scan Software Ltd in ways that require 6 Scan Software Ltd to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that 6 Scan Software Ltd gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask users of our site protection services to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with 6Scan – by purchasing access to premium protection services, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, 6 Scan Software Ltd collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with 6Scan. 6 Scan Software Ltd does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
6 Scan Software Ltd may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites and their protected sites. For instance, 6 Scan Software Ltd may monitor the most widely-found security vulnerabilities and/or code versions6 Scan Software Ltd may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, 6 Scan Software Ltd does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
6 Scan Software Ltd discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 6Scan’s behalf or to provide services available at 6 Scan Software Ltd websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using 6Scan’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 6Scan will never rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, 6 Scan Software Ltd discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when 6Scan believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 6Scan, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an 6 Scan Software Ltd website and have supplied your email address, 6 Scan Software Ltd may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with 6 Scan Software Ltd and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 6Scan takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 6Scan uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of 6Scan website, and their website access preferences. 6Scan visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 6Scan’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of 6Scan’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**  
If 6 Scan Software Ltd , or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that 6 Scan Software Ltd goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of 6 Scan Software Ltd may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, 6 Scan Software Ltd may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in 6Scan’s sole discretion. 6 Scan Software Ltd encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you use 6Scan’s site protection services, you should also check your dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site and/or site protection services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. (This policy is based in part on Automattic’s Privacy Policy, kindly published under the Creative Commons Sharealike license.)
